<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<content>
	<section name="information">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				As an initiate of the Technomagi order, you find yourself thrown into an instance that has been long forgotten since 
				the dawn of the order. Using your nanites powerful extrapolation capabilities, you must study your surroundings and 
				attempt to survive here, filling your surroundings with the sorts of technology that you're familiar with.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="true" specialisation="cleric">
				As the cleric you have been given a base bit of research towards knowledge topics that fall under your realm of expertise. 
				Your affinity with other technomages and organic creatures as a whole will shine through when you come to use abilities, items, 
				recipes and other such things that are relevant to your choice of path.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="true" specialisation="engineer">
				As the engineer you have been given a base bit of research towards knowledge topics that fall under your realm of expertise. 
				Your affinity with machines, devices and nanites shine through when you come to use abilities, items, 
				recipes and other such things that are relevant to your choice of path.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="true" specialisation="scholar">
				As the scholar you have been given a base bit of research towards knowledge topics that fall under your realm of expertise. 
				Your thirst for knowledge and information will shine through when you unlock knowledge or come to use abilities, items, 
				recipes and other such things that are relevant to your choice of path.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="true" specialisation="guardian">
				As the guardian you have been given a base bit of research towards knowledge topics that fall under your realm of expertise. 
				Your skills as a warrior and your desire to protect others will shine through when you come to use abilities, items, 
				recipes and other such things that are relevant to your choice of path.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="true" specialisation="shadow">
				As the shadow you have been given a base bit of research towards knowledge topics that fall under your realm of expertise. 
				Your affinity with the arcane will shine through when you come to use abilities, items, 
				recipes and other such things that are relevant to your choice of path.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="false">
				
			</paragraph>
		</page>	
	</section>
	<section name="staff">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				To get started with your abilities you'll need to craft yourself a staff. Once you've crafted a basic staff, simply right click 
				and your nanites will surge the staff, activating it.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph multiplayer="false">
				Since you have multiplayer mode disabled, you switch between the specialisation staffs by placing it on its own in the crafting bench.
			</paragraph>
			<recipe alignment="center" type="vanilla" output="item:Technomagi:staff_basic" />
			<recipe alignment="center" type="vanilla" output="item:Technomagi:staff_cleric" multiplayer="false" />
			<recipe alignment="center" type="vanilla" output="item:Technomagi:staff_scholar" multiplayer="false" />
			<recipe alignment="center" type="vanilla" output="item:Technomagi:staff_guardian" multiplayer="false" />
			<recipe alignment="center" type="vanilla" output="item:Technomagi:staff_engineer" multiplayer="false" />
			<recipe alignment="center" type="vanilla" output="item:Technomagi:staff_shadow" multiplayer="false" />
		</page>
	</section>
</content>