<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<content>
	<section name="cleric">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				The cleric path is one chosen by those who value life above all else.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				Technomages who choose to follow the cleric path, are for the most part, empathetic, caring individuals, who accept the 
				responsibility of the life of others without a second thought.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				As a cleric you receive increased regenerative capabilities, allowing you to tend to the wounds and needs of others without 
				worrying about yourself.
			</paragraph>
		</page>
	</section>
	<section name="scholar">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				The scholar path is one chosen by those who seek knowledge and understanding wherever they may be, and wherever 
				that may take them.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				Some scholars consider themselves to be the superior technomages, but a true scholar would know that they are 
				simply a small part of a large machine, and without their fellow technomages, that large machine would fall apart.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				As a scholar you receive a random research boost while collecting data on knowledge topics.
			</paragraph>
		</page>
	</section>
	<section name="guardian">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				The guardian path is one chosen by those who strive for strength in the pursuit of protecting others.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				Guardians are the frontline of the technomage world, their job is to defend and protect their fellow technomages by 
				putting their life on the line. For the most part, technomage warriors will if possible, seek an option that does not require fighting.
			</paragraph>
			<paragraph>
				As a guardian you receive the ability to endure more physical damage compared to your fellow technomages.
			</paragraph>
		</page>
	</section>
	<section name="shadow">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				Sneaky sneaky
			</paragraph>
		</page>
	</section>
	<section name="engineer">
		<page>
			<paragraph>
				They like stuff!
			</paragraph>
		</page>
	</section>
</content>